chris gardner
chris gardner
how are you
Nasılsın
good morning
Günaydın
chris gardner
chris gardner
chris carter good to see you again
chris carter seni tekrar görmek güzel
chris gardner pleasure
chris gardner zevk
i&#39;ve been sitting out there for the last
Son dakikaya kadar orada oturuyordum
half hour trying to come up with a story
yarım saat bir hikaye bulmaya çalışmak
that would explain my being here
bu benim burada olmamı açıklar
dressed
giyinmiş
like this
bunun gibi
and and i wanted to come up with a story
ve ve bir hikaye uydurmak istedim
that would demonstrate qualities that
bu, niteliklerini gösterecek
i&#39;m sure you all admire here like like
eminim hepiniz burada hayranlıkla izliyorsunuz
earnestness
samimiyet
or diligence and
veya çalışkanlık ve
team playing to something and i couldn&#39;t
takım bir şeye oynuyordu ve ben yapamadım
think
düşünmek
of anything
herhangi bir şeyin
so the truth is
yani gerçek şu ki
i was arrested for failure to pay
ödeme yapmadığım için tutuklandım
parking tickets parking figures
park cezası park rakamları
and i ran all the way here from the polk
ve ben Polk'tan buraya kadar koştum
station the police station
karakol polis karakolu
what were you doing before you were
sen olmadan önce ne yapıyordun
arrested i was uh
tutuklandım ben uh
painting my apartment
dairemi boyuyorum
did you dry now
şimdi kurudun mu
i hope so
Umarım
jay says you&#39;re pretty determined oh
jay oldukça kararlı olduğunu söylüyor oh
he&#39;s been waiting outside the front of
o, ön tarafta bekliyordu
the building with some 40-pound gizmo
40 kiloluk bir alete sahip bina
for over a month
bir aydan fazla bir süredir
he said you&#39;re smart
o senin akıllı olduğunu söyledi
i&#39;d like to think so
öyle düşünmek isterim
and you want to learn this business yes
ve bu işi öğrenmek istiyorsun evet
sir i want to learn this business have
efendim bu işi öğrenmek istiyorum
you already started learning on your own
Zaten kendi başına öğrenmeye başladın
absolutely
kesinlikle
jay yes sir
jay evet efendim
how many times have you seen chris
Chris'i kaç kez gördün?
no i don&#39;t know
hayır bilmiyorum
one too many apparently
görünüşe göre bir fazla
has he ever dressed like this no
hiç böyle giyinmiş miydi
no
HAYIR
jacket and ty
ceket ve ty
first in your class
sınıfının birincisi
in school
okulda
high school yes sir
lise evet efendim
how many in the class
sınıfta kaç kişi var
uh 12. it was a small town
uh 12. küçük bir kasabaydı
i&#39;ll say but i was also first in my
diyeceğim ama ben de ilk bendim
radar class in in the navy and that was
Deniz kuvvetlerinde radar sınıfı ve bu
a class of 20.
20 kişilik bir sınıf.
can i say something
bir şey söyleyebilir miyim
um
bir
i&#39;m the type of person
ben öyle bir insanım
if you ask me a question and i don&#39;t
eğer bana bir soru sorarsan ve ben de cevap vermezsem
know the answer
cevabı biliyorum
i&#39;m gonna tell you that i don&#39;t know
sana bilmediğimi söyleyeceğim
but i bet you what
ama bahse girerim ki
i know how to find the answer and i will
cevabı nasıl bulacağımı biliyorum ve yapacağım
find the answer
cevabı bul
is that fair enough
bu yeterince adil mi
chris
İsa
what would you say
ne derdin
if a guy walked in for an interview
eğer bir adam mülakat için içeri girseydi
without a shirt
gömleksiz
on and i hired him what would you say
ve onu işe aldım ne dersin
he must have had on some really nice
gerçekten güzel bir şeyler giymiş olmalı
pants
pantolon
[Laughter]
[Gülüşmeler]
chris
İsa
i don&#39;t know how you did it dressed as a
Bunu nasıl yaptığını bilmiyorum, giyinmiş olarak
garbage man but you really pulled it off
çöp adam ama sen gerçekten başardın
in there thank you very much mr twistle
orada çok teşekkür ederim bay twistle
hey now you can call me jay all right
hey artık bana jay diyebilirsin tamam mı
we&#39;ll talk to you soon all right so i&#39;ll
tamam yakında konuşacağız o yüzden
let you know jay
sana haber vereyim jay
you&#39;ll let me know jay
bana haber vereceksin jay
what do you mean yeah i&#39;ll give you a
ne demek istiyorsun evet sana bir tane vereceğim
call tomorrow sometime what what are you
yarın bir ara ne yapıyorsun
talking you hounded me for this you
konuşuyorsun bunun için beni rahatsız ettin
stood here listen there&#39;s no salary no i
burada durdum dinle maaş yok hayır ben
was not aware of that my circumstances
koşullarımın farkında değildim
have changed some and
biraz değişti ve
i need to be certain that i&#39;ll be able
Yapabileceğimden emin olmam gerekiyor
to
ile
okay
Tamam
tonight
bu akşam
i swear i will fill your spot i promise
yemin ederim ki senin yerini dolduracağım söz veriyorum
you i&#39;ll look like if you back out you
eğer geri çekilirsen sana benzeyeceğim
know what i&#39;ll look like to the partners
ortaklara nasıl görüneceğimi biliyorum
yes and ass
evet ve eşek
an ass
ve
all the way
tüm yol boyunca
you are a piece of work
sen bir iş parçasısın
tonight
bu akşam
you
Sen